《绿箭》前情回顾
Previously on "Arrow"...
所以我的弟弟是个幽灵
So my brother's a ghost?
十年前  我发现你在贩毒
10 years ago, I found out you were dealing.
是的  你说服我参军
Yeah. You convinced me to enlist.
■
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
-约翰  -你看到了他以前是什么样
- John. - You saw what kind of man my brother was,
现在是什么样
what kind of man he is.
翻译   OphiaSaaaga Reginamoon
他是你的家人  你说过他是个好人
He's your family. You said he was a good man.
或许他仍然是
Maybe part of him still is.
我不知道
I don't know.
翻译    Silence Michael TvYoung
翻译    ET外星人 桃子西 天青月白
快趴下
Get down.
她脊椎神经上的损伤  是永久性的
The damage to her spinal cord, it's permanent.
校对   苹果果 Michael  精校   陈小圈
她再也没法走路了
She's never gonna walk again.
时间轴风吹来的那片云
再不快点回家
If we don't get home soon,
保姆就要多收一小时钱了
the sitter's gonna charge us an extra hour.
特效&后期   咖啡Lee[绿箭侠]       总监   苹果果
我们该坐车回去的
We should have taken the car.
保姆半个小时多收15块吗
Sitter's what, another 15 bucks for half an hour?
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
再多一倍也值得
It's a bargain at twice the price.
莱拉
Lyla.
-天呐  -艾伦
- Dear God. - Alan?
抱歉在这美好的夜晚打扰你们
Sorry to crash your evening.
那就别打扰  像一般人那样打个电话
Then don't. Just call like normal people.
我做的可不是一般的工作
I don't have a normal job,
况且我已经暴露了
and I've been compromised.
我已经退出超能力联合调查组了
I'm not ARGUS anymore.
所以你是我唯一信任的人
Which makes you the only person I can trust.
我需要你告诉沃勒...
I need you to tell Waller--
趴下
Get down!
你中枪了
You're hit!
艾伦
Alan!
约翰
Johnnie!
你没事吧
Are you OK?
你说得对
You were right.
我们该坐车回家的
We should have taken the car.
绿 箭
第四季  第十一集
小心  慢点  慢点
Just be careful. Slow down, slow down.
小心  小心  小心
Careful, careful, careful.
你想让我小心吗
Do you want me to be careful?
你现在是升级版的奥利弗  对吧
Oh, this is more Oliver 2.0, isn't it?
你以为卖萌就能分散我的注意力吗
You think being cute is gonna distract me?
任务圆满完成
Mission accomplished.
你不用无微不至地照顾我
You don't have to wait on me hand and foot,
不过  能再来条毛毯就更好了
though I wouldn't say no to a blanket.
医生说要坚持吃两片
The doctor says stick with the two tablets
才能抑制你的疼痛
to keep with your current pain management regimen.
我真的很感激你所做的一切
You know, I really appreciate what you're doing,
但你还要拯救城市
but you have a city to save,
还要竞选市长
a mayoral campaign,
还要对付一个能用意念移动物体的
a freaky superbad who can move things
变态大恶人
with his mind.
这些跟你的康复比起来
None of which are nearly as important
都是小事
as your recovery.
谢谢
Thank you.
我猜达克想要毁灭的
I think the people in the city
这座城市的市民可能不会同意
that Darhk wants to destroy might disagree.
那些人应该明白
Well, those people should know that
没有你的帮助  我对付达米恩·达克
I stand no chance of stopping Damien Darhk
毫无胜算
without your help.
但你不得不去
Well, you might have to.
我脊髓受损
I have a spinal cord injury.
可能永远也不会完全康复
I might never make a full recovery ever.
这是最坏的情况
That is worst case scenario,
而且不管怎样  你都是
and either way, you are still
团队的核心成员
a vital member of the team.
你的超能力在于你的头脑
Your superpower is right there.
或许我的新代号可以叫"火辣轮椅"
Maybe my new code name could be Hot Wheels.
多想想
Keep pitching on that.
不开玩笑了
All jokes aside,
就像你说的
like you said,
我给团队的贡献在于我的头脑
what I do bring to the team is my mind,
但现在我脑子里很乱
and there's a lot on it.
跟我说说
So talk to me.
我觉得我还没准备好回归团队
I just don't think I'm ready to come back yet,
在你命悬一线的的情况下
and the last thing you need
最不需要的就是为我分心
in a life-or-limb situation is me.
看来我们要暂时对这个问题
Wow. We are going to agree to disagree
保留不同意见了
on that one for the moment.
怎么了
What's going on?
约翰和莱拉被袭击
John and Lyla were attacked.
天呐  他们还好吗
Oh, my God! Are they ok?
约翰中枪了  皮肉伤
John was shot. It was a flesh wound.
我该去看看他们
I should go see them.
我们该去看看他们
We should go see them.
想得美
Nice try.
晚餐在冰箱里
Dinner is in the fridge.
放烤箱220度加热
Reheat in the oven at 425 degrees.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
然后他们就把你丢下了
And they just left you there?
是啊  还给我留下了这伤口
Yeah, but not before leaving me with this.
确定不是蜂巢吗
We are sure that this wasn't HIVE?
这些人看着像军人
These men looked military.
对  但你说张说他暴露了
Right, but you said that Chang said he was compromised,
他明确地告诉你去找沃勒
And he specifically told you to go and speak with Waller.
以我对她的了解  她一定
Knowing her, she had Alan working
派艾伦开展了秘密工作
on something off the books.
我得打个电话给保姆
I need to call the sitter.
好
OK.
我们要尽快找到张
We need to find Chang before
以免事态恶化
this kidnapping becomes something worse.
那辆车没有挂车牌
Yeah, well, the van didn't have any plates on them,
张的手机是超能力联合调查组配的
and Chang's phone is ARGUS-issued,
所以无法追踪信号
which means it will be untraceable.
我们现在需要费利西蒂的帮助
We could really use Felicity's help right now.
她还没准备好
Yeah. She's not up for it yet.
我可以让星城警署查查有没有案件
I can have SCPD see if John's bullet
跟打中约翰的子弹有关
is connected to any open cases.
好
Yeah.
我可以去犯罪现场看看有没有遗漏的证据
I can go check the crime scene for any leftover evidence.
你该去星城总院检查一下
You should go to Starling General and have that looked at.
我没事
I'll be fine.
为什么
Why?
因为吃芝士汉堡是更好的选择吗
Because eating a cheeseburger is a better option?
这不是给我的
This isn't for me.
是给安迪的
It's for Andy.
你的手臂怎么了
What happened to your arm?
没什么  普通工伤
Nothing. It's an occupational hazard.
我从没想过你会是面具义侠这种人
I never pegged you for the masked vigilante type.
是吗  我想我俩都是满身惊喜的人  安迪
Yeah? Well, I guess we're both full of surprises, Andy.
你知道吗
You know what?
你不断到这下面来
You keep coming down here,
问这问那的
asking me all these questions,
但我从没问过你问题
but I never get to ask them back.
你想知道什么
What do you want to know?
你的办公地点怎么变成了一间地下室
How do you end up working out of a basement
就我们待的这地方
or wherever we are
还和一个穿着绿兜帽的家伙一起打击罪犯
and fighting crime with a guy who wears a green hoodie?
他是个好人
Well, he's a good man,
而且我们不是在打击罪犯  安迪
and we're not fighting crime, Andy.
这是一个自强不息的城市
Taking a city that's holding itself together,
而我们在帮助它
and we are helping.
你忘了那曾经也是你的任务吗
Don't you remember when that was your mission?
很高兴你俩自愿来参加这次任务
Appreciate you two volunteering for this mission.
有机会和我弟弟一起出战
Chance to ride with my little brother?
我可不会错过
Wouldn't miss it.
是啊  塔利班可对付不来狄格尔兄弟
Yeah. The Taliban's not ready for the Diggle brothers.
阿富汗  赫尔曼德省  2005年
总部盯上了
HQ's got eyes on
一批用于资助当地军火贸易的高品质鸦片
a primo opium shipment that's been funding the local arms trade.
我们把货截了
We cut them off,
恐怖分子们就只能用石头木棍和我们作战了
the terrorists will be left with nothing but rocks and sticks to fight us.
收到  长官
Copy that, sir.
你准备好了吗
You ready for this?
好了
Yeah.
来了  不要留情  伙计们
Incoming. Stay frosty, boys.
收到
Copy that.
火箭筒
RPG!
警戒周边
Perimeter!
上
Go!
快  快  快
Go! Go, go, go!
快走  快走  快走
Move, move, move, move, move!
他们要是从另一边过来我们就完了
We're screwed if they come around the other side.
我看能不能为我们争取点时间
I'll see if I can buy us some time.
快走  快走
Move, move.
我能把他们引到这东西那里
I can draw them to it.
好的  我掩护你
I got you. I'll cover.
快  快  快
Come on, come on, come on!
埋好了
It's in!
安迪
Andy!
醒醒啊  老弟
Talk to me, man.
没事吧
You OK?
我们搞定他们了吗
Did we get them?
你搞定他们了  老弟
You got them, brother.
走吧
Let's go.
为何我没被邀请参加这个伤心派对
Why didn't I get invited to this pity party?
是谁
Hello?
至少你选对了派对小礼物
At least you found the right party favors.
3片药有点多
3 pills is a bit much,
但我有什么资格评论呢
but who am I to judge?
好吧  不管你是谁
OK. Whoever you are,
你在错误的夜晚  惹上了不该惹的女人
you picked the wrong woman on the wrong night to mess with.
拜托
Please.
你我都清楚你什么都做不了
We both know you're in no position to do anything.
假如你可以  你早就回到外面去了
If you did, you'd be back out in the world
而不是在这里耗着
instead of holed up here.
天呐  怎么回事
Oh, my God. What is going on?
发生什么事了
What is going on?
天呐
Oh, my God.
天呐  我疯了
Oh, my God. I am losing it.
我完完全全彻彻底底地疯了
I am completely and utterly losing it.
现在我在自言自语了
Now I'm talking to myself.
其实不算
Not exactly.
警戒线
劳蕾尔·兰斯  地检办公室
Laurel Lance, District Attorney's office.
这里什么情况
What do we have here?
死亡男性  35岁左右  亚洲人
Deceased male, around 35, Asian,
多处撕裂伤  挫伤
multiple lacerations, contusions,
还有钝器所致的外伤
and blunt force trauma.
你们询问过周边人员了吗
You canvass the area yet?
也许有目击证人看到了什么
There could be a witness who saw something.
我不需要一个助理地检来对我指手画脚
I don't need an ADA to tell me how to do my job.
我确定外面那个杀人犯
Well, I'm sure there's a murderer out there
会感激你这么不主动的
who appreciates your lack of initiative.
动手吧
Go ahead.
私人保安在夜班一开始的时候发现了他
Private security found him at the start of a graveyard shift.
是张
That's Chang.
干这事的人是把他折麽死的
Whoever did this took their time.
膝盖有多处撕裂伤
Multiple lacerations to the knees,
手臂断了一只  至少三块指甲被拔掉了
a broken arm, at least 3 pulled fingernails.
他们是有目的地折磨他
They were torturing him for something.
他们想要的不止是信息
Information wasn't the only thing they wanted.
我告诉过你们了  张探员的任务不关你的事
I told you. What Agent Chang was working on is none of your concern,
更不关你的事
and it's even less of yours.
我还以为在你发现
Thought would change
张被打残  折磨  杀害之后
once you found out Chang was mutilated,
事情有所改变呢
tortured, and killed.
恐怕你高估了我们对你的欢迎  狄格尔先生
I'm afraid you've overextended your welcome, Mr. Diggle.
在超能力联合调查组这就是"滚出去"的意思
Which is A.R.G.U.S. speak for get the hell out of here.
真聪明
You always were a quick study.
我说这句话是真心实意的
I mean this with all sincerity.
我真的很想念你
Your presence has truly been missed.
即便我没有表现出来
Even if I don't show it,
但我对张先生的逝世深表遗憾
I am deeply regretful for Mr. Chang's death.
希望我们下次能在愉快一点的情况下见面
Hopefully we'll meet again under happier circumstances.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
当然
Of course.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
你怎么这种表情
Hey. What was that look all about?
酮咯酸  也许会有副作用
Ketorolac. Possible side effects include
包括手脚肿胀
swelling of the hands and feet,
食欲增加  有感染的风险
increased appetite, risk of infection.
真好  我出现幻觉了
Oh, good, good, good. Hallucinations.
我真的以为自己不会这么蠢
I really thought I was smarter than this.
你不是我  而且你绝对是幻觉
You are not me, and you're definitely not real.
我以前就是你
I used to be you,
或是你以前就是我
or you used to be me--
坚强  自信  一头黑发
Strong, confident, brunette--
但你把这些全都浪费在扮演超级英雄上
but you wasted all that away to go play superhero,
现在看看你的下场
and look where that got you.
等一下  这个沃勒说
OK. So wait. This Waller person said
她什么也不能告诉你
that she couldn't tell you anything
却把这个U盘给了你
and then gave you that flash drive?
超能力联合调查组有全天候内部监控
ARGUS has 24/7 internal surveillance.
她不想任何人知道
She didn't want anyone to know she was giving me
她给了我什么
what she was giving me.
问题是她到底给了你什么
The question is what did she give you?
我以前见过这符号
I've seen that symbol before.
其实是个标志
It's a Default actually.
暗影塔楼就是美军特种部队
Shadowspire is a U.S. Army Special Forces Unit.
三年前他们在艾伦·张负责的一项行动中
ARGUS took them down 3 years ago
被人揭发以战争牟利
when they were exposed as war profiteers
然后超能力联合调查组把他们取缔了
in an OP run by Alan Chang.
那另外两个人呢
What about those other two guys?
报告说他们已经失踪两天了
They've been reported missing for two days.
如果他们就是暗影塔楼
If those were the missing agents
失踪的部分特工
that were a part of Shadowspire, then--
那其余的暗影塔楼肯定是在执行报复行动
Then the rest of Shadowspire is gonna be on a payback mission.
在那两名特工像艾伦一样惨遭毒手之前
We need to find the other two agents
我们要找到他们
before they end up like Alan.
我有发现
Hey. I think I found something.
沃勒给你的U盘上的标志
That Default that was on the flash drive that Waller gave you.
暗影塔楼
Shadowspire.
我觉得我在哪见过
I thought I recognized that from someplace.
在阿富汗时  我碰到过这些人
I ran into a bunch of those guys back in the Afghanistan.
我要再和我弟弟谈谈
I need to talk to my brother again.
谁会想到没收的鸦片装运奖励
Who would think the reward for confiscating
还会有额外的保护呢
an opium shipment would be additional duty guarding it?
难道你想总统赐你一吻吗
What you expect, a kiss from the president?
我的两名征服者怎么样了
How are my two conquering heroes?
汗如雨下  疲惫不堪
Wet and tired.
我们状态良好  长官
We are good, sir.
你们今天做得非常好
You gentlemen did good today.
谢谢  长官
Thank you, sir.
有没有想过将来离开这鬼地方做什么
Ever think about your future beyond working in this hell hole?
不知道
I don't know.
也许做做保安  保镖吧
Personal security, bodyguarding maybe.
你们注定要干一番大事业
You boys are meant for better things.
如果在早上之前
The 3 of us could make bank
几包毒品正巧擅离职守
if a few bricks of that sweet Afghani powder
我们三个人就能大捞一笔
happened to go AWOL before the morning.
我不得不谢拒此事  长官
You know, I'm gonna have to decline, sir.
我妈妈教我绝对不要相信肮脏的战争牟利者
My mama taught me never to trust dirty war profiteers.
也许你该注意一下你的语气
You should probably watch your tone.
你的下场可能会比昨天那些人还惨
You might end up in worse shape than those talis yesterday.
继续站岗
As you were.
-瞧瞧你  -你在说什么呢
- Well, look at you. - What you talking about?
在星城  你会迫不及待地抓住
Back in Starling, you would have jumped at any opportunity
任何获得小营小利的机会
to earn a little extra scratch.
你受到了这地方的熏陶嘛
This place has been good for you.
我为你骄傲  安迪
I'm proud of you, Andy.
你到底效力过多少邪恶组织
So exactly how many evil organizations are you associated with?
我已经数不清了
I'm beginning to lose count.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
暗影塔楼
Shadowspire!
你以往的军队同事来了星城
Your old army buddies are in Starling City.
他们虐待并杀死了超能力联合调查组的一名特工
They tortured and killed an ARGUS agents
还掳走了另外两名特工
and abducted two others.
我现在和他们已经没有关系了
Look. I have nothing to do with them anymore.
我退役之后  他们就和我断绝了关系
After I got discharged, they cut ties.
他们只要现役军人
They only want enlisted men.
我怎么没料到这点呢
How the hell could I not see this?
你当时一直和我在一起
You were with me the entire time!
因为你只看到你想要看的
Because you saw what you wanted to see.
你想要相信军队
Look. You wanted to believe that the army
改变了我
had straightened me out.
我是你弟弟
Look. I'm your brother,
但是我生来和你不同
but I'm not built like you.
我不像你那样喜欢参军
I didn't take to the military like you did.
你把世界看成是需要修补的事物
You saw the world as something to be fixed.
我只看到它遭到破坏
I only saw it as broken,
所以我确保自己能生存下去
so I made sure I had enough to survive in it.
所以你在你自己哥哥面前
So you pretended to be a completely different person
假装是一个完全不同的人吗
around your own brother?
请不要摆出这一副臭脸给我看
It spared me the look that's on your face right now.
但也许我们能利用这一点
But maybe some good could come out of this.
安迪
Andy...
你在说什么
what are you talking about?
那两名失踪的特工
The two missing agents--
你觉得他们还活着吗
you still think they're alive?
-我可以希望  -我可以帮忙
- I can hope. - And I can help.
我知道暗影塔楼的行事方法
Look. I know how Shadowspire operates.
如果他们行事如前的话
If they're consistent,
那他们就会利用最近的自由港做为作战基地
they'll use the nearest Freeport as a base of operations.
隐藏非法赃物的最佳地点就在
The best place to hide illicit things
合法地点的旁边
is right next to legitimate ones.
那地方叫做自由港
It's called a Freeport
在世界各地运输途中
it holds commodities while they're in transit
这些地方暂时储存货物
between international destinations.
很低级
Pretty low-end.
看来有人升级了安全系统
Looks like somebody upgraded their security system.
传感器  激光绊线  智能锁
Motion sensors, laser tripwires, digital locks.
我想我知道谁能帮上忙
I think I know somebody who can help.
奥利弗  来电
不打算接吗
Not gonna get that?
很明智
Smart move.
奥利弗
Oliver?
我在外面执行任务
I'm out in the field actually.
我们遇到点技术难题
We've come up against some tech,
对你来说是小菜一碟
the kind that you typically eat for breakfast.
我知道你说过
Now I know that you said you're not
你还没有准备好开始工作
ready to get back in the saddle,
可是我们真的需要你帮助
but we could really use your help.
你不会再上那个当了  是吧
You're not really falling for that again, are you?
你在哪
Where are you?
太平洋自由港  是个
Pacific Freeport. It's a--
安保系统解除了
Security's down.
太厉害了
That was amazing.
看来你已经回归了
All you need to do is get back in the game.
真让人觉得恶心
I thought vomiting inside my mouth was just an expression.
我黑进了他们的安保系统
I'm inside their security system.
我看到了7个挺吓人的保安
I got eyes on 7 very menacing-looking fellows
正在看守着一些集装箱
guarding a bunch of holding containers.
我收到了其中一个集装箱的红外线
I'm reading infrared on one of the containers.
我正在想办法打开它的锁
I'm working on opening that lock.
你们去救人质  我们来搞定暗影塔楼
Go for the hostages. We'll take care of shadowspire.
集装箱开了  应该在你们前方3米
Container's open. Should be 10 feet in front of you.
第二个集装箱在你们右边
Second container on your right.
找到了
Got it.
我们找到超能力联合调查组的人了
We found the two ARGUS agents.
他们都死了
They're both dead.
那就赶紧离开那
Get out of here then.
你和斯巴达怎么样了
What about you and Spartan?
我们能搞定  快走
We got this. Go!
费利西蒂  怎么回事
Felicity, what's going on?
我不知道  我
I don't know. I--
我肯定是触发了什么失效保护装置
I must have tripped some sort of failsafe.
系统因为收到太多请求而超负荷了
The system's overloaded with too many requests.
真糟糕
Oopsie.
我听过很多治安维持者的事迹
You hear so much about these vigilantes,
可是我从来没亲眼见过
but I've never seen one in person.
我可知道你这个冷血杀手
Wish I could say the same about a cold-blooded murderer.
我们以前认识吗
Have we met before?
好了  我们走
All right. Let's go.
我跟斯巴达汇合了  我们没事
I've got Spartan. We're good!
都不是你的功劳
No thanks to you.
你还好吗
You OK?
看情况
That depends.
约翰没事吧
Is John OK?
约翰很好
John's fine,
可是你好像觉得
But you seem to think that
今晚的事是你的错
what happened tonight is your fault.
我很确定是我
Well, I'm pretty sure I was the one
没能阻止那扇门关闭
who couldn't stop the security doors from closing.
你之前说得很清楚没有准备好
And I'm the one who pushed you to get involved
可是我还是强迫着你参与到其中的
when you signaled pretty hard that you weren't ready.
我并没有说得
I wasn't signaling...
那么清楚
that hard.
很抱歉我逼你了
I'm sorry that I pushed.
我是觉得只要你把手放到键盘上
I just thought that if you got behind a keyboard again
一切就会又恢复正常了
that things would just start to feel normal.
真高兴做超级英雄就是我们认为的正常
I love how playing superhero is what we consider normal.
可是已经不可能恢复正常了
But there is no going back to normal.
你懂我的意思
You know what I mean.
我知道你的意思
I know what you mean.
但我的意思是我们不能再成为你们中的一员了
What I mean is that I can no longer be a part of the team.
因为你的伤吗
Because of your injury?
你不能让这事影响你
You can't let that stop you.
但它真的影响了
Except it has.
看看我  奥利弗
Look at me, Oliver.
我已经在这里待了一周半了
I've spent the last week and a half stuck in this loft.
我没法走路  没法开车
I can't... move. I can't drive.
我连下楼去买杯咖啡都做不到
I can't walk down the street and get a cup of coffee,
如果今晚的事说明了什么
and if tonight is any indication,
那就是我连本该能做的事
I can't do the one thing
现在都做不了了
that I'm supposed to still be able to do.
你只是需要点时间
You just need to give it time.
跟我聊聊
Hey. Talk to me.
说吧  告诉他
Go ahead. Tell him.
告诉他你出现幻觉了
Tell him you're hallucinating.
就像《流氓扫荡者》的剧情那样
That should go over like Gangbusters.
我不会假装说我明白
I'm not going to pretend that I understand...
快点  费利西蒂  告诉他
Come on, Felicity. Tell him. Tell him...
你现在的感受
what you're going through,
可是你是我认识的最坚强的人
but you are the strongest person that I know...
你不适合再在团队里了
that you're no good for the team anymore,
我们会像你支持我们一样地来支持你
and we have your back the same way that you have our back.
不仅腿废了
that in addition to having legs that don't work,
而且还总是
you've got a full on case of the crazies...
我们昨晚没能搞定那些人
We don't stand a chance to take down those guards last night--
出现幻觉
seeing visions...
别说了
Just shut up!
我不是那个意思
I didn't mean that.
我也不是想惹你生气
I didn't mean to upset you.
不不不  不是说你  不是说你
No, no, no. It's not you, it's not you.
能不能让我一个人静静
Can I just be alone for a little while?
我本来还希望着
You know, I guessed I hoped
告诉你暗影塔楼的事之后
by giving you intel on Shadowspire
你就会放我出来
you would let me out of my cell,
这可不是我所想象的
but this isn't what I had in mind.
你好  莱拉  好久不见
Hey, Lyla. It's been a while.
安迪
Andy.
狄格尔先生
Mr. Diggle.
我是超能力联合调查组的主管
I'm the director of ARGUS.
死去的那三个是我的人
Those 3 dead men were my agents.
我想了解你跟暗影塔楼的关系
I want to debrief you on your relationship to Shadowspire.
真有意思  上次我们见面的时候
Which is interesting because you couldn't even
你根本就没提过暗影塔楼
say Shadowspire last time we met.
我是针对潜在漏洞
I was taking an understandable precaution
而做出的合理预防
in light of a potential security breach.
你今晚发现的两名特工
The two agents you found tonight
被指派护送被收缴的电磁炮运输
were assigned to safeguard a shipment of confiscated railguns.
这是一次绝对的秘密行动
But that was a completely black assignment,
所以我很感兴趣暗影塔楼是怎么知道的
so I'd be very interested to know how Shadowspire knew about it.
阿曼达  你没意识到更严重的问题吗
Amanda, you don't see the bigger problem here?
这些东西可以发射出电磁弹
Those things fire off electromagnetic projectiles.
只要一发就能摧毁一栋楼
Just one of them could take down a building.
-你的意思是  -我的意思是
- Your point? - My point...
如果暗影塔楼在寻求这种指示
is that if Shadowspire's looking for that type of ordinance--
我更担心的是
I'm far more concerned
在我的组织里存在
with a catastrophic security breach
灾难性的安全漏洞  狄格尔先生
in my organization, Mr. Diggle.
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
暗影塔楼要的不是电磁炮
Shadowspire's not after railguns.
如果你错了呢  安迪
And what if you're wrong, Andy?
我们以为你和暗影塔楼没关系了呢
We thought you weren't hooked up with Shadowspire anymore.
是没有了  但我知道他们如何运作
I'm not, but I know the way they work.
暗影塔楼擅长调虎离山
Shadowspire's all about misdirection.
一支精锐部队
An elite military unit?
那只是犯罪组织的幌子
A cover for a criminal organization.
一次电磁炮劫运吗
A heist of a shipment of railguns?
不是的
No.
这是声东击西
Distraction.
他们要的是别的东西
They're after something else.
你想谈谈吗
You want to talk about it?
有什么好谈的
What is there to talk about?
费利西蒂很难过
Felicity's upset,
我不知道怎么帮她
I don't know how to help her.
这很直截了当吧
It seems entirely straightforward.
作为这里唯一有幸和你
As the only other person here who's had
交往过的人  我提个建议
the privilege of dating you, a piece of advice.
好吧
OK.
别对自己太苛刻
Don't be so hard on yourself.
这一切都是我的错
Everything that's happening is my fault.
我知道你会这么说
I knew you were gonna say that.
上个月  我们对抗汪达尔·萨维奇时
Last month when we went up against Vandal Savage,
巴里做了时间旅行
Barry traveled through time
改变了一些事
and changed things.
你说什么
Uh, what?
巴里会时间旅行
Barry can travel through time,
他警告我  当你改变过去时
and he warned me that when you change the past
过去会制造报应  所以这几个月
the past fights back, so for the past month,
我一直被这个想法所困扰
I have been tortured by the idea
要是我听了他的话
that what happened to Felicity might have happened
也许费利西蒂就不会出事了
because I wouldn't listen to him.
费利西蒂的遭遇只能怪一个人
The only person who is responsible for what happened to Felicity
就是达米恩·达克
is Damien Darhk.
约翰
John.
这就去
We're on it.
约翰认为暗影塔楼要抢劫电磁炮运输
John thinks Shadowspire's going after a shipment of railguns.
-帮我打给西娅  -没问题
- Can you call Thea? - Got it.
奥利弗
Hey, Oliver.
费利西蒂会自己做选择  你知道的
Felicity--she makes her own choices, you know.
我相信这也是你这么爱她的原因之一
I'm sure that's one of the reasons why you love her so much.
知道了
Yeah.
《闪灵》啊
"The Shining."
不知道我该感到荣幸还是受辱
Not sure if I should be flattered or insulted.
我的天啊  去死  快消失
Oh, my God. Die. Just go away already.
由于我就是你
Since I'm you,
这可能有点难办  不是吗
that could be a little difficult, don't you think?
好吧
Fine.
我在这  你也在这
I'm here, you're here,
这是为什么
so why are we here?
你除了跟我针锋相对
Do you have anything the least bit interesting to say to me
没有半点有趣的事可以说吗
besides the little jabs you keep making?
这些都是为了引起你注意
Those jabs are just to get your attention.
所以你要对我说什么
So what do you want to tell me?
我不是来说的  我是来让你看的
I'm not here to tell you anything. I'm here to show you.
上次我们还是这个造型时  库柏制造了假死
The last time we looked like this, Cooper had just fake died.
这和我前男友有什么关系
What does this have to do with my ex-boyfriend?
我们以为他死了那天
The day we thought he died,
你把头发染了
you broke out the hair dye,
删掉了联系人  然后决定
ditched the contacts, and decided
以后再不依靠任何人的帮助
you weren't gonna rely on anyone else for help
绝不
ever again.
只会是你自己对抗全世界
It was just going to be you against the world,
那将成为你的盔甲
and that was going to be your armor.
我猜我会选防弹衣
Guess I should have chosen kevlar.
停下吧  别再自怨自艾了
Stop it. Stop feeling sorry for yourself
别再假装了
and stop pretending!
假装什么
Pretending?!
假装这样的你是真的你
Pretending that this is the real you--
一头金发  戴着眼镜
The blond hair, the glasses,
理智的时尚感
the sensible fashion.
人们戴面具是有理由的
People wear masks for a reason--
为了隐藏真实的自己
to hide who they are--
你这五年不就是这么做的吗
just like you have been doing for the past 5 years.
你先是决定成为
First, you decided to sign up for being
全世界最大材小用的IT女
the world's most overqualified I.T. girl,
然后又决定成为英雄
and then you decide to try being a hero,
看看这些给了你什么
and look what it got you,
从今以后你只能坐观战席了
a ringside seat to the rest of your life.
你以为你很了不起吗
You thought you were such a badass.
沃勒说电磁炮就在那辆货车后面
Waller says the shipment of railguns is in the back of that truck,
一小时之内出发
moving out in less than an hour.
暗影塔楼要一车电磁炮做什么
What does Shadowspire want with a whole shipment of railguns?
肯定不是什么好事
Absolutely nothing good.
你能回来真好  麦考斯特工
It's nice to have you back, Agent Michaels.
感觉一如从前
Feels like old times.
一如从前的是你隐瞒秘密
What feels like old times is you keeping secrets
让无辜人丢了性命
that get good people killed.
你有没有想过
Did it ever occur to you that Alan
如果你把反暗影塔楼行动摆到台面上
and the other two agents might still be alive if you hadn't
艾伦和另外两名特工可能就不会死了
tried to keep your Anti-Shadowspire operations off the books?
当然想过
Of course it has,
但我们事业不光彩的一面
but the ugly side of our business
就是有时必须要用牺牲换取安全
is that sometimes security has to be paid for in blood.
谢谢  我还在想我为什么离开呢
Thank you. I was wondering why I'd left.
我不知道你在担心什么  伙计
I don't know what you're worried about, man.
你的团队今晚在外面执行任务
Your team's out seeing action tonight.
而我没有跟他们一起是因为我要在这里照顾你
And I'm not with them because I'm here babysitting you.
他们在哪里
Where are they?
有点不对劲
Something's wrong.
安全级别9
电磁炮的车上没动静
There's no movement on the railgun ship--
举起手来
Your hands up.
放到脑后
Behind your heads now.
放下
Don't do it.
阿曼达  好久不见
Amanda, it's been ages.
乔伊纳中尉  真希望我能说很高兴见到你
Lieutenant Joyner, wish I could say it was a pleasure.
伙计  别动了
Oh, man. Stop moving.
你都把我弄晕了
You are making me dizzy.
天啊
Oh, my god.
我跟你说过  约翰
I told you, John.
电磁炮就是用来声东击西的
The railguns were a distraction.
超能力联合调查组才是终极目标
ARGUS is the endgame.
如果这是为了报复
If this is retribution for the work
我和张特工使暗影塔楼受创的事
Agent Chang and I did crippling Shadowspire,
看来我们的工作还做得不够好
clearly it didn't take.
报仇和报复都是无用的追求
Vengeance and retribution are useless pursuits.
首先  它们没有回报
For one thing, they don't pay.
我是为了卢比孔河行动而来
I'm here for Rubicon,
而你  你要给我进去的密码
And you--you're gonna give me the codes to access it.
你知道我不能这么做
You know I can't do that.
我知道  所以我才让这些人都活着
I do. That's why I kept all these people alive.
我给你20分钟
I'm gonna give you 20 minutes,
然后
and then...
我会再问你一次
I'm gonna ask you again.
该死
Damn it!
他们一定是这里放了干扰发射器
They must have jammers in here.
没有移动网络或无线信号
No cell or wi-fi service.
你愿意跟我解释一下吗
Uh, would you like to share with the rest of the class?
这些监视器的工作原理跟电视一样
These monitors work just like TVs,
接收700兆赫的广播信号
Receiving broadcast signals on the 700 megahertz band.
我有个朋友很喜欢这种东西
I have a friend who's into this kind of stuff.
偶尔我会听听她说什么
Occasionally, I listen to her.
如果我能把芯片组转换成传输模式
If I can just switch the chipset into transmitting mode,
我应该就能联系上我的队员
I should be able to contact my team.
莱拉可没有时间等你的队员
Oh, man. Lyla does not have time to wait on your team.
我们要做点什么
We've got to do something.
是吗  你不能做任何事  安迪
Yeah? Well, you're not doing anything, Andy.
你妻子在那里
Look, man. Your wife is in there!
现在不是怀疑我的时候
Now's not the time to not trust me.
快点  快点  快点
Come on, come on, come on.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
你就是在我面前演戏的是吗
You were just putting on a little show for me, huh?
放手  你怎么回事
Get your hands off me, man. What's wrong with you?
我看到你跟乔伊纳混在一起
I see you buddying up with Joyner,
跟他聊天  交情不浅
talking to him, thick as thieves.
你能冷静一下吗
Would you relax?
我们是在聊21点牌
We were talking about blackjack.
我告诉他
I was telling him about
你教我的牌点计算技巧
the card counting technique you taught me.
-真的吗  安迪  -没错
-Really, Andy? -Yeah, really.
好吧
Ok, man.
我不能再让你堕落了
Because I can't have you backsliding, all right?
我答应了来参军
Man, I agreed to go through this whole army thing,
我遵守了我的诺言
and I kept my end of the bargain.
现在我要你遵守你的
Now I need you to keep yours.
我想让你开始像兄弟一样对待我
And I need you to start treating me like a brother
而不是像个罪犯
and not like a criminal.
好
Ok.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你是对的
You're right.
约翰  暗影塔楼没有对动手
John, Shadowspire never made a move on the shipment,
所以无论他们下一步要做什么...
So whatever their next move is, it...
都不会是电磁炮
It's not railguns.
你弟弟那里有什么新消息就打电话给我
Just call me when you get something new from your brother.
好的
All right.
真开心我们的新据点有升降设备
I am so glad our new lair has elevator access.
柯蒂斯说要做我的专属司机
Curtis has anointed himself my personal chauffeur.
很好  他没问很多
Fancy. It's a good thing he didn't ask
怎样半夜来你竞选办公室的事
too many questions about coming to your campaign office
真是太好了
in the middle of the night.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我刚刚在家
Well, I was at home,
突然觉得
feeling more self-pity
前所未有地自怨自艾
Than I have in my entire life when it hit me.
这才是我该做的事
This is who I am.
我想要参与你的超级英雄冒险
I wanted to come along on your awesome superhero adventure
因为我想帮助别人
because I wanted to help people.
过去的我对世界太愤怒了
And the old me was so angry at the world,
那种愤怒没完成过任何一件事
but that anger never accomplished anything.
它只是创造更多的愤怒
It just created more anger
和一些坏极的个人造型选择
and some seriously bad personal style choices.
我想要做点好事
I wanted to do some good in the world.
我刚刚说得那么好
That was a good speech.
还以为你会觉得很棒
I thought you'd be a little more impressed.
确实说得很好  但是
It was a good speech, but...
但是  怎么说的来着
But...how did it go again?
我很了解你
I know you and I do
你可能觉得发生的这一切都是你的错
You're probably thinking what happened was your fault.
我是来告诉你这不是你的错
I'm here to tell you that it's not
也不是我的错
And that it's not mine either.
这只是一个人的错
It's the fault of only one man,
他还有一个
And he has an extremely
很押韵的名字
on-the-nose and alliterative name.
而我们将去阻止他
And we're going to stop him.
不是出于愧疚或报复  或悔恨
Not out of guilt or vengeance, or regret.
我们将去阻止他是因为那是我们该做的事
We are going to stop him because it's what we do.
我们就是这样的人
That's who we are.
说得不错
That was a good speech.
很开心能听到你这么说
I'm very happy to hear it.
我们需要加点斜坡了
Uh, we're gonna need to get some ramps.
超能力联合调查组被偷袭了
ARGUS has been compromised,
而且莱拉被劫持成人质了
and Lyla's being held hostage.
我在你的办公室发现了这个
I found this in your office.
希望你不要介意
Hope you don't mind.
中尉  我们发现了一封来自看守区域发出的
Lieutenant, we picked up an unauthorized comm
未经授权的通信
out of the detention area.
找个人去看看怎么回事
Take someone and look into it.
是  长官
Yes sir.
来点酒吧
Go on.
你恐怕再也没有享受它的机会了
You might not get the chance to enjoy it again.
已经过去了20分钟
It's been 20 minutes.
需要我再次帮你的组织裁减一下人手吗
Am I gonna have to downsize your organization yet again?
显然需要
Apparently.
好吧  你真是太冷血了
Well, that's rather cold-blooded.
你真的一点也不了解她  是吗
You really don't know her that well at all, do you?
麦考斯女士是我最为信任的特工之一
Ms. Michaels is one of my most trusted agents.
她比任何人都清楚
She knows better than anyone
我完全能够不动声色地看着你
that I'm perfectly capable of watching you
处决掉这个房间里的任何一个人
execute every person in this room,
而且我还是绝对不会给你卢比孔河行动的密码
and I'll still never give you the Rubicon access codes.
是这样吗  麦考斯女士
Is that right, Ms. Michaels?
没错
It's right.
这就是我离开的原因
It's why I left.
阿曼达·沃勒在做出决定时从来不会
Amanda Waller doesn't make decisions based on
考虑人命的价值
the value of human life.
真遗憾
Pity.
不要
No!
好吧  麦考斯女士  最可靠的特工
Well, Ms. Michaels, most trusted agent,
你现在还剩下20分钟
looks like you now have 20 minutes.
约翰
John.
上帝啊  不  不
Oh, my god. No. No!
约翰  约翰  约翰
John, John, John.
约翰  住手  他会杀了她的
John, please! He's gonna kill her.
你一定得相信我  否则后果很严重
You can't afford not to trust me.
“守望者”  我们到了
Overwatch, we're on site.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我觉得你是时候起一个代号了
Well, I thought that it was time you got a code name.
-你觉得如何  -太棒了
- What do you think? - It's perfect.
本来想用“神谕”的  但有其他人用了
Was gonna go with Oracle, but it's taken.
暗影塔楼将整个C&C区域都封锁了
Shadowspire's got the entire area around C&C in lockdown.
你们几个是唯一的希望了
You guys are the only game in town.
你能把我们弄进去吗
Can you get us inside?
你是说像这样吗
Like that you mean?
好吧  你们总算找到我了
Well, it's about time you guys came looking.
你是干什么的
Who the hell are you supposed to be?
安德鲁·狄格尔警官
Sergeant Andrew Diggle,
第五四二军团  第五作战营
52nd regiment, 5th battalion.
你为什么被关在这儿
What are you doing locked up here?
说来话长
It's a long story,
简单点说  都怪我那混蛋哥哥
shorter version being my brother's a jerk.
但我很走运  你们的指挥官和我有过交情
Lucky for me, though, your Co and I go way back.
如果你们真的想从莱拉·麦考斯那里
If you're serious about Lyla Michaels
拿到卢比孔河行动密码
giving up the Rubicon codes,
你还不如打开无线电  告诉乔伊纳中尉
you will get on the radio and tell Lieutenant Joyner
那个教会他如何算牌的家伙在这儿
the guy that taught him how to count cards is here.
而且  打算帮他一把
And, uh, wants to help him out.
安德鲁·狄格尔
Andy Diggle?
你都死了还看起来这么好
You look pretty good for a dead man.
我还以为我长胖了呢
Here I thought I put on weight.
你在超能力联合调查组干什么
What are you doing at ARGUS,
而且还活着
much less alive?
阿曼达·沃勒带我进来的
Amanda Waller brought me in
因为我之前和你们的人有过联系
because of my former association with you guys,
但是  世界真小
but, uh, small world, though.
你的朋友麦考斯女士
Your friend Ms. Michaels--
是我的嫂子
She's my sister-in-law.
-安迪  -也就是说
- Andy. - Point being,
他的丈夫此刻正藏身在
her husband is crawling around
这些通风井道里
these ventilation shafts right now.
如果你用枪指着他
If you put a gun on him,
她就会告诉你所有你想知道的
she'll tell you whatever you need to know.
你这混蛋
You son of a--
嘿
Hey.
背叛自己的兄弟  可真够冷血
Turning on your own brother. That's ice-cold.
好吧  你最清楚不过了
Well, you know better than most.
我和约翰从来都看不对眼
John and I never saw eye to eye.
伙计  去检查一下通风管道设备
Gentlemen, check the facility's ventilation shafts.
情况如何
Overwatch?
C&C区域  三楼下面  最北角
C&C, 3 floors down, northeast corner.
好的  给我们一点时间
Well, give us a few minutes.
另一个狄格兄弟
The other Diggle brother.
真有趣
Isn't this quaint?
等我挣脱这些桎梏  我会给你点厉害看看
I get out of these cuffs, and you'll see you think I can be.
太可惜了  你一点也不像你的弟弟
It's a shame you can't be more like the little Diggle.
他的实用主义看来让他受益匪浅
His pragmatism has proven to be quite the asset.
如果你的弟弟所言是对的  你应该能够
Now if your brother's right, you should be able
说服你的妻子交出
to convince your wife to give me
我想要的东西
what I want.
约翰尼  如果卢比孔河行动密码被公之于众
Johnnie, if Rubicon ever got out in the open--
麦考斯女士  五秒钟后
Ms. Michaels, in 5 seconds,
你丈夫的脑袋将会血浆四溢
it's your husband's brains that will be out in the open.
四
4...
三
3...
二
2...
动手吧
Do it.
告诉他们吧  莱拉
Do it, Lyla.
没关系的
It's all right.
很好
Excellent.
如果你能搞定这些家伙
If you've run out of guys to punch,
就去支援一下那个视死如归的英雄吧
spartan needs an assist,
实际上需要两个人去前支援
Two assists actually.
告诉我们要做什么
Tell us what to do.
暗影塔楼正从在逐步从安全库中
Shadowspire's getting the access codes
获取通行密码
for a secure vault in the sublevel.
我正在设法阻止密码的运转
I'm trying to stop the codes from working,
但是我需要黑金丝雀和快手
but I'm going to need Canary and Speedy
确保我能够成功
as my insurance policies.
你需要我去哪儿
Where do you want me?
你花的时间太久了
This is taking too long.
有些不对劲
Something's wrong.
有人锁定了我的系统
Someone's locking me out of the system.
走开
Go away.
我已经不是你了  很久之前就不是了
I'm not you anymore. I haven't been for a long time.
我进不去
I can't get in.
我的密码没有错
I have all the right codes,
但是外部有人在阻止我
but someone on the outside is preventing me
登陆进入地下金库
from entering the sublevel vault.
那可真不幸
That's extremely unfortunate.
-你还好吗  -没事
- You ok? - Yeah.
你们呢
You ok?
我们没事
Yeah, we're fine.
干得好
Good job.
就像你说的
It was like you said.
这是让我们两个都能进入的方法
It was the only way to get us both in here.
记住这可是我的主意
Just remember whose idea this was.
你还想干什么
Eh, what were you expecting,
总统给你个亲吻吗
a kiss from the president?
敬阿曼达·沃勒
To Amanda Waller?
To Amanda Waller.
你还记得那时她试图
You remember that time that she tried
用无人机轰炸掉一个城市吗
to take down the city with a drone strike?
美好时光啊
Good times.
谢谢你今晚的帮助
Hey. Thanks for the assist tonight.
很高兴能帮上忙
I'm just glad to be useful.
你修改保安系统时做得很棒
Good job jury-rigging the security system, though.
只想让你为我骄傲  费利西蒂
Just trying to make you proud, Felicity.
我很骄傲
You did.
你想怎么处理安迪
What are you gonna do about Andy?
还没有想好
Still haven't made a decision on that.
哪怕他刚刚救了你的命
You mean, even though he just saved you life?
当然  但你们也出了很大的力气
Yeah, well, you guys had a whole lot to do with that,
但你说的对  这是我八年来第一次
but you're right. This is the first time in 8 years
感觉到他是我弟弟
I've seen shades of my old brother.
你想见我  长官
You wanted to see me, sir?
我已经拿到我的部分了
Already got my cut.
这是老板欣赏你的额外奖励
Eh, it's a token of appreciation from the boss.
用鸦片换了别的东西
Traded the opium for something else.
比如说什么
Like what?
你自己问他吧
Ask him yourself.
很感谢你的帮助  狄格尔先生
Thank you for your assistance, Mr. Diggle.
乔伊纳中尉很赞赏你
Lieutenant Joyner sings your praises.
很高兴能帮忙
Happy to help.
你拿鸦片换什么
What did you get for the opium?
传说中提起过一个拥有无限力量的地方
Legend speaks of a place of immeasurable power.
很多前往搜寻它的人都失踪了
Many have disappeared searching for it,
那么多人失踪  当地人把那里称为
so much so that the locals simply refer to it by one word--
炼狱
Purgatory.
我还以为我们已经全都收拾完了
I thought we were totally unpacked.
拆开看看
Just humor me.
是什么
What am I getting?
是的  那个白色的盒子
Ah, yes. The white box.
对  对  对
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
准备好了吗
Ahh. You ready?
当你说你做过一些个人风格错误的选择时
When you said that you made some bad personal style choices,
你真没有开玩笑
you weren't kidding.
这是原来的我
This is the old me,
一个桀骜不驯的黑发黑客
a rebellious brunette hacker
从不遵守别人的任何规则
who didn't listen to anyone else's rules but her own.
你已经不再是那样的人了吗
You're not that person anymore?
不是了
Nope.
你昨晚做的事情很棒
What you did last night was amazing.
-我确实很棒  -是的
- I was really badass. - Yeah.
但是过去的我估计会偷走
Though the old me probably would have stolen
卢比孔河行动的计划  然后公开它们
the plans for Rubicon and released them
作为某种政治宣言
as some sort of political statement.
过去的我会拧断乔伊纳的脖子
The old me would have snapped Joyner's neck.
没错
Yeah.
我们都成长了
We've both grown.
谢谢你一直在我身边
Thank you for always being on my side.
我只想在你身边
No place I'd rather be.
把垃圾桶递给我  还有这打火机
Hand me that garbage can and this lighter.
你吃了些什么药
How much medication are you on?
什么都没有
Absolutely none.
只是想保证我的过去只是过去了
Just want to make sure that my past stays the past, you know?
还有一件事
One more thing from me.
医生说你的情况是永久的
The doctor said your condition is permanent,
我觉得我们两个不应该
and I don't think that it's healthy
继续拒绝接受现实
or productive for either of us to live in denial,
但是我见过能缩小会飞和奔跑如闪电的人
but I have seen people speed and shrink and fly.
还见证了我们的朋友起死回生
We watched a friend of ours come back from the dead.
那才是我们生活的世界
That is the world we live in now...
我不会停止搜寻的
And I will never stop searching it.
直到我们能找出让你重新走路的办法
Until we find a way to make you walk again.
你确定要这么做吗
Are you sure about this?
因为我不确定
'Cause I'm not.
总比关在笼子里好  对吧
Better than being in the cage, right?
接下来交给我就好
I'll have him from here.
不用拘束
Make yourself comfortable.
莱拉在做饭
Lyla was cooking something.
这是关于重新和卡莉还有安迪见面
This is about reconnecting with Carly and Andy,
我明白  安迪
I get it, Andy.
慢慢来  对吧
Step by step, right?
安迪
Andy?
我在做烤猪肉
I'm making pork roast.
-约翰说那是你的最爱  -没错
- Johnny said it's your favourite. - Yeah.
确实是
Yeah, it is.
我还准备了一个惊喜  稍等一下
I got another superise for you, man. Just a second.
-莱拉  我  -别说了
- Lyla, I...  - Not a word.
约翰和我都同意这样做了
John and I both agree to this.
她很激动要见到你
She is excited to meet you.
这是你侄女
This is your niece.
莎拉  这是你叔叔安迪
Sarah, that's your uncle Andy.
安迪
Hi, Andy.
她眼睛像她妈妈
She's got mom's eyes.
欢迎回家  兄弟
Welcome home, man.